Malcolm S. Knowles Papers
Malcolm S. Knowles Papers
- Workshop files
  - University of Michigan School of Dentistry, 1977; faculty retreat (Box 63)
  - University of Missouri Cooperative Extension Service
    - Evaluating your professionalism as an adult educator, 1973 (Box 63)
    - Workshop, 1973 (Box 63)
  - University of Missouri Extension Association, undated; professional improvement workshop (Box 63)
  - University of Nevada National College of the State Judiciary
    - Training workshop for judge faculty, 1977 (Box 63)
    - Training workshops, 1975-1976 (Box 63)
  - University of North Carolina Education Department, ED 510, 1979 (Box 63)
  - University of Southern California School of Public Administration Center for Training and Development
    - Public administration courses, 1980 (Box 63)
    - Public administration problems 501, 1977 (Box 64)
  - University of West Indies Department of Extra-Mural Studies
    - Leadership training, 1967 (Box 64)
    - Principles of working with groups, 1967 (Box 64)
  - University of Toronto School of Continuing Studies
    - Andragogy workshops, 1976; 2 folders (Box 64)
    - Self-directed learning, 1977-1980; 4 folders (Box 64)
  - Wascana Institute of Applied Arts and Sciences - Department of Continuing Education workshop, 1976 (Box 64)
  - Wayne State University School of Social Work, 1976; field instructors' workshop (Box 64)
  - West Virginia University School of Nursing, Understanding the adult learner, 1973 (Box 64)
  - Western Electric Company, Incorporated
    - Management training program, 1963; 1980; 2 folders (Box 64)
    - Management sensitivity training, 1969 (Box 64)
  - Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education, 11th annual training institute for psychiatrists-teachers of practicing physicians, 1971 (Box 64)
  - Westinghouse Electric Corporation
    - Executive course, 1975-1976; 2 folders (Box 64, 65)
    - Executive forum, 1977 (Box 65)
  - Willamette University Oregon Judicial College, Continuing education of trial judges workshop, 1977 (Box 65)
  - York University Centre for Continuing Education, Group process and organizational skills institute, 1969 (Box 65)
  - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA)
    - Association program for professional development, 1968 (Box 65)
    - Eastern association program for professional development, 1962-1968 (Box 65)
    - Eastern region adult program, 1982 (Box 65)
    - Eastern unit organization development project, 1965 (Box 65)
    - Midwest association program for professional development, 1966-1968 (Box 65)
    - New England area council interracial practices workshop, 1967 (Box 65)
    - Canada
      - Association program for professional development, 1967-1969 (Box 65)
      - National Council Leadership development lab for program secretaries, 1964 (Box 65)
      - National Council Leadership development program for secretaries, 1963 (Box 65)
      - National CouncilStaff workshop, 1960 (Box 65)
    - Organization Development Project, 1960-1961 (Box 65)
    - Organization Development Project, 1962 (Box 66)
    - Southwest and West Central Area Councils, Trainers' lab, 1969 (Box 66)
    - Southwest Area Council Association program for professional development, 1966-1968; 3 folders (Box 66)
    - Southwest Area Council Manpower development project, 1974 (Box 66)
- Audio-visual material
  - Graphics
    - Straight talk, developed by Larry Nolan Davis (Box 69)
  - Films
    - Dynamics of leadership, 8 reels (Box 69)
  - Videotapes
    - International Federation of Training and Development Organizations World Congress, 1982; VHS (Box 69)
  - Audiocassettes
    - Administrator as self-directed learner, by Malcolm S. Knowles (Box 69)
    - American Society for Training and Development, Competency based education (Box 69)
    - American Society for Training and Development, 37th annual conference, 1981 (Box 69)
    - American Society for Training and Development, National conference, 1984; 1986 (Box 69)
    - North Carolina State University Spring Seminar Series, Non-traditional study, by Cyril O. Houle, 2 tapes (Box 69)
    - Southern Extension Conference, Problem clinic on adult learning, by Malcolm Knowles (Box 69)
    - Sub-master A-1 and A-2, 2 tapes (Box 69)
  - Reel-to-reel
    - Council on Social Work Education, 1971 (Box 69)
    - Hard look at adult christian education, by John Fry, and Another hard look at adult christian education, by Malcolm Knowles, 1963 (Box 69)
    - Clarification on issues: hard look-revisited, by John Fry and Malcolm Knowles, with dialogue, 1963 (Box 69)